We wish you a merry Christmas
我们祝你圣诞快乐
And a happy New Year
祝你新年快乐
Day one: time to get my list in shape
头天  调整好我的日程
Christmas is around the corner
圣诞节就要来了
So much to do, not a moment left to wait
好多事要忙  没有时间能浪费
Have to get it done before the holidays are here
得赶在节日之前都准备妥帖
It's that Christmas time of year
今年的圣诞佳节
So everypony sing
来  大家一起唱
We wish you a merry Christmas
我们祝你圣诞快乐
And a happy New Year
祝你新年快乐
Through the streets of boutiques
走进街边的精品屋
Picking out the perfect presents
挑选最好的礼物
Every shop, have to stop
每一样  都要挑
Try to find the perfect gift
只为最棒的贺礼
Now the tree has to be
圣诞树得要是
Just the perfect one – that's it! That's the one!
那最完美的  没错  就这样
Every light shining bright
每束光都闪亮
Starting from the base to tip
把整棵树都照耀
Have to bake  decorate
来烘焙, 做装缀
Now I need the perfect dress – a success!
完美服装不能少  十分好
Oh, no, I can't be late
噢  千万别迟到
I've got Pinkie Pie's party date
还有萍琪派的派对
Where everypony sings
和大家一起唱
We wish you a merry Christmas
我们祝你圣诞快乐
And a happy New Year
祝你新年快乐
Ponies caroling, singing songs we know and love
大家齐欢唱  歌颂熟知的曲调
Music fills the air, rising to the stars above
音乐装满堂  直冲天外上云宵
Watching snow, reading by the fire
炉火边  瑞雪伴书香
Family close, stockings hung with care
亲朋会  长袜挂壁上
Outside those ponies singing merrily
看窗外  大家欢笑又歌唱
Listen close as they start to sing
仔细听  它们齐开腔
We wish you a merry Christmas
我们祝你圣诞快乐
And a happy New Year
祝你新年快乐
Time to stop and count my blessings
该停下开始做祷告
Put the craziness aside
把狂热放一旁
Christmas only comes around once a year
每年只会有一次圣诞节
And every year fills my heart with pride
而每次都深感到自豪
When everypony sings
当大家同唱
We wish you a merry Christmas
我们祝你圣诞快乐
And a happy New Year
祝你新年快乐
翻译
蛟龙
润色
校对
蛟龙  Loadhe
背景图绘制
Wing
时间轴
Loadhe
制作
习成 PBU 工作组
感谢观看